Guide to the Central Washington University Athletics Department, Team Sports Collection 1923-2007 (bulk 1965-1995)
Central Washington University Archives and Special Collections
- Scrapbooks, XI
  - Baton - NCAA Track and Field Championships - Division II Outdoor - ACU, 2005- (Box-folder 176-11)
  - Baton - NCAA Track and Field Championships - Division II Outdoor - ESU, 2006- (Box-folder 176-12)
  - Baton - NCAA Track and Field Championships - Division II Indoor - Stonehill College and the Reggie Lewis Track and Athletic Center, 2007- (Box-folder 176-13)
  - Baton - NCAA Track and Field Championships - Division II Outdoor - CSPU, 2008- (Box-folder 176-14)
  - Baton - NCAA Track and Field Championships - Division II Outdoor - ASU, 2009- (Box-folder 176-15)
  - Baton - NCAA Track and Field Championships - Division II Outdoor - Johnson C. Smith University, 2010- (Box-folder 176-16)
  - Baton - NCAA Track and Field Championships - Division II Outdoor - Bradenton, Florida, 2016- (Box-folder 176-17)
  - Baton - NCAA Track and Field Championships - Division II Outdoor - Bradenton, Florida, 2017- (Box-folder 176-18)
  - Baton - NCAA Track and Field Championships - Division II Indoor - Pittsburg, KS, 2019- (Box-folder 176-19)
  - Baton - NCAA Track and Field Championships - Division II Outdoor - Pueblo, CO, 2023- (Box-folder 176-20)
  - Baton - NCAA Track and Field Championships - Division II Outdoor - Kingsville, TX, 2019- (Box-folder 176-21)
  - Baton - NCAA Track and Field Championships - Division II Outdoor - Charlotte, NC, 2018- (Box-folder 176-22)
  - GNAC Women's Cross Country Champions Banner, 2004- (Box-folder 176-23)
  - GNAC Men's Outdoor Track and Field Champions Banner, 2006- (Box-folder 176-24)
  - GNAC Men's Outdoor Track and Field Champions Banner, 2007- (Box-folder 176-25)
  - GNAC Men's Indoor Track and Field Champions Banner, 2007- (Box-folder 176-26)
  - NCAA 'Make It Yours' Division I Token (Box-folder 176-27)
  - Track - 16mm Film, 1964- (Box-folder 177-1)
  - Relay - 16 mm Film (Box-folder 177-2)
  - 16 mm Film (Box-folder 177-3)
  - 16 mm Film (Box-folder 177-4)
  - 16 mm Film (Box-folder 177-5)
  - Clover Park High School - 16 mm Film (Box-folder 177-6)
  - Pole Vault - 16 mm Film (Box-folder 177-7)
  - Shot Put - 16 mm Film (Box-folder 177-8)
  - Track - 16mm Film (Box-folder 177-9)
  - Steeple Chase Discus and Shot - Conference - 16 mm Film, 1970- (Box-folder 177-10)
  - Pole Vault - Steel Pole - 16 mm Film (Box-folder 177-11)
  - 8 mm Film (Box-folder 177-12)
  - High Jump - 16 mm Film (Box-folder 177-13)
  - 16 mm Film (Box-folder 177-14)
  - Javelin - 16 mm Film (Box-folder 177-15)
  - CWSC Football - Individual Shots - 16 mm Film (Box-folder 177-16)
  - Football - 16 mm Film (Box-folder 177-17)
  - Discuss - 16 mm Film (Box-folder 177-18)
  - 8 mm FIlm (Box-folder 177-19)
  - 16 mm FIlm (Box-folder 177-20)
  - 16 mm FIlm (Box-folder 177-21)
  - 8 mm Film (Box-folder 177-22)
  - Nationals - Bob Johnson, Dave Hegland, Finals - Film, 1975- (Box-folder 277-23)
  - 8 mm Film (Box-folder 177-24)
  - Mike Daniels, Mitch Ring, Dave Hegland, Nationals - 8 mm Film, 1975- (Box-folder 177-25)
  - 8 mm Film (Box-folder 177-26)
  - NAIA Cross Country - 8 mm Film, 1975- (Box-folder 177-27)
  - VHS (Box-folder 177-28)
  - House of Representatives Resolutions, 1989-2000 (Box-folder 178-1)
  - Hall of Fame Certificates, 2007- (Box-folder 178-2)
  - Showdown in the Sound, 2005- (Box-folder 178-3)
  - Hall of Fame Nominations, 2007-2008 (Box-folder 178-4)
  - Hall of Fame Correspondence, 2008- (Box-folder 178-5)
  - Game Contracts, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 178-6)
  - Golf Tournament, 2003- (Box-folder 178-7)
  - 3rd and 6th Annual Wells Fargo/CWU Golf Challenge Hosted By Jon Kitna, 2005-2008 (Box-folder 178-8)
  - A Tribute to the Nicholsons Celebration, 1998- (Box-folder 178-9)
  - Nicholson - Articles and Event Photographs, 1998- (Box-folder 178-10)
  - Battle in Seattle, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 178-11)
  - NAIA Award Certificates, 1957-1995 (Box-folder 178-12)
  - Battle in Seattle, 2005-2006 (Box-folder 179-1)
  - Battle in Seattle, 2007-2009 (Box-folder 179-2)
  - Contracts, 2003-2006 (Box-folder 179-3)
  - CWU Athletic Advisory Board Meeting, 2005- (Box-folder 179-4)
  - Hall of Fame Banquet Pamphlet and Volleyball Team Thank You Card, 2011-2012 (Box-folder 179-5)
  - Photographs and Signed Wellington Portrait (Box-folder 179-6)
  - Discs - Sportsmanship Softball Video, Changes to Nicholson Pavilion Video, Pep Band Video, Softball Slideshow Video, Football Video, 2008-2010 (Box-folder 179-7)
  - Helms Hall - Hall of Fame Award Honoring Leo Nicholson (Box-folder 180-1)